[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Jinna, I really like you.
You know how hot Jinna is, right?
You've been practicing hard today, so I got you some water.
You're serious about my friend, right?
Does it seem like I'm not?
I only want you to pretend to hit on me.
Don't get too attached.
I don't like pretending, though.
Just get to the point already.
I'm actually going to hit on you.
No deals, no ulterior motives.
This award is for you all.
I wonder how prestigious your damn award really is?
Do you know that you are the problem in this family?
I do!
You only consider those you deem useful to you. That's it!
Honey!
Will there be a day when my dad accepts me?
At the end of the day, I feel like I can never truly be myself
as long as I'm still alive.
It's because you never cared about him.
If there's anything else you need about Anda, just let me know.
I'm actually not crying, you know?
Right. Just come with me and wash your face.
What are you looking at?
The one who wasn't crying.
You love teasing people?
My friend's dead.
Let me cry for a bit, okay?
I miss him whenever I'm on the road.
Jinna.
Maybe you don't know it yet, but I really love Anda as an actor.
He's my source of joy.
It broke my heart when someone insulted him.
I was happy when someone complimented him.
And when this happened to him,
I could barely hold myself together.
If you're hurting, just let it out.
Don't worry about how people will see you.
He was your best friend, Jinna.
Everyone understands you.
Can I hug you?
What are you guys doing?
I'm just stretching.
[Characters, places, and incidents in this production]
[are entirely fictitious.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
Point B.
1.462...
62...
0.132...
So what is it, Jinna?
It's a murder case, isn't it?
I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
People on the internet are just guessing away.
But I think there might be something to the idea that Anda didn't take his own life.
Yeah.
I don't think he did it, either.
That's Anda we're talking about.
Our friend, Anda.
Jinna, what do you think?
He definitely didn't take his life.
That's all I know.
- Hey! - Whoa!
Got bored of your phone or something?
You just tossed it away.
Well, you just showed up out of nowhere.
- You startled me. - I was calling you from way over there.
You were sitting here spacing out.
You're allowed to grieve over Anda's death,
but don't waste your feelings on those crazy people online.
I don't want to overthink it, but have you seen what they're saying?
They're saying Anda was just trying to get attention.
See? That's what I meant. Give it to me.
I know you're sad, but there's nothing we can do.
Do you understand, Podduang?
Why?
He was in so much pain.
Why did his life have to end like this?
Even after he's gone, people still won't stop hurting him.
I understand, but there's nothing we can do.
Let me see. Are you crying?
I'm not.
Look at you.
We're the same age, but why do I feel like you're still a kid?
Maybe it's because you're big.
Is that an insult?
I'm your best friend, you know.
Return this for me.
Thanks a lot, Dunk.
Here, have something sweet.
Anyway, this helps.
Every time she sends me a screenshot, the battery is in the red.
But wait...
There are kiosks everywhere.
I borrowed it for you, and now I have to return it?
Why? Can't you just do that for me?
Fine, I will.
- What are you smiling at? - Yeah, you've been smiling for a while now.
It's just that I'm glad to have you two as my friends.
What?
Is something the matter?
I didn't see you at lunch, so I came up to check on you.
And you're not eating?
If you were in my shoes, would you be able to eat anything?
My brother just died.
If you're not feeling up to it, you can take a break.
I'll take care of this case myself. Don't worry.
And did you find anything else?
I'm going through the CCTV footage.
He parked in a very secluded spot, so I have to check it thoroughly.
Anyway, the forensic report says he died of suffocation.
Did your brother often fall asleep in the car?
Yes.
When he was sleepy, he tended to just pass out.
Actually, my mom had warned him about it.
I'm being serious here.
You also think this doesn't look like suicide, right?
Yeah, I've been thinking the same thing.
I know depression is unpredictable, but I don't think that's what's going on here,
even though he was on sleeping pills regularly.
That's right.
They found that it was a very mild sleeping pill,
and there wasn't a large amount in his system.
I was actually the last person to see him.
Why did I let him drive all by himself?
Where did you two split up?
At a restaurant near our house.
Like I said, Anda moved into a condo,
so I had to plan to meet up with him and catch up.
He seemed perfectly fine, though.
We were both acting very normal.
I was even complaining to him
about how he used my car but wouldn't go get it washed.
Why?
What happened, Lieutenant?
Itti,
I promise you, if someone's behind this,
they're going to jail.
Don't worry. We'll do everything we can for you.
Thank you very much, Lieutenant.
If you find out where he went or who he met after he left me,
tell me.
I might know something.
My family and I will fully cooperate.
Of course.
Stop reading the comments about Anda.
These people online are just talking nonsense.
It's not like there are many.
Most of them are just asking about the cause of death.
What do you think, though?
Do you think Anda was murdered?
I think...
he might have been murdered.
Preliminary forensic results suggest
the cause of death may be suffocation.
However, authorities are still examining the evidence
and gathering more details to determine the cause of death.
Amp, are you taking out the trash?
Yes.
Amp, are you all right?
Anda didn't take his life.
Anda didn't kill himself.
It's true!
We need to help him. Find the culprit.
We need to help Anda. You must help Anda!
She was talking like she was out of it.
Then she suddenly ran into her room.
I didn't even get to ask her anything.
I'm so confused.
She's a fan, so she must be grieving, too.
That's why she's been acting a bit off.
I'm a fan, too.
I've been moping all day.
Podduang.
Do you also think that Anda was murdered?
Yeah, I think so, too.
Then how about we both try to uncover the truth?
What truth?
The truth about who actually killed him.
Please, Podduang.
Help me find them.
Consider it a final favor for Anda.
Let's help Anda.
Podduang.
Have you eaten anything?
I have.
And have you slept at all?
Here.
It's the one I borrowed.
And you just bought a new one?
Yeah. I lost yours, so I bought a new one to replace it.
You guys don't have to worry about me.
I can eat and sleep,
but I just can't stop thinking about it.
How can I help you?
Bum...
What the hell is this?
What is it?
[Breaking! Leaked Messages May Solve Star's Death]
[Let's break up, Anda.] [What happened, Kum? Why?]
[I'm sorry, Anda.] [Kum, you're not like this. What's wrong?]
[Let's break up, Anda.]
[Anda's boyfriend? Who is he?] [Is the chat real?]
[Is Kum involved in Anda's death?] [Stop guessing blindly.]
[They broke up on the day he died. Is that a coincidence?]
[Was this the reason he took his own life?] [Please respect the deceased and the family.]
Is that chat real?
Is this person named Kum involved in this matter?
I only know as much as you do.
And what do you think?
I don't think it was Kum.
Why are you so sure?
I know him. He wouldn't do it.
How can you trust someone so easily?
[Interrogation Room]
When was the last time you saw the deceased?
In the morning...
before he left the condo.
Were you two living together?
Yes.
We were dating.
Where were you throughout that day?
Did you meet the deceased again?
Where were you?
I...
I had something to do at a friend's house.
Do you know where the deceased's phone and laptop are?
I don't.
I...
I searched all over the condo but couldn't find them, as I already said.
Do you know the phone passcode of the deceased?
I do.
He knew mine, too.
Do you know where the deceased's phone and laptop are?
I don't know, officer.
I told you already.
Then tell me, who was the friend you visited that day?
I can't tell you.
If you give us something that could help,
it'll be better for you and your boyfriend.
You're aware of that, right?
So why can't you tell us where you were?
Personal reasons.
Then do you think anyone else was involved?
I really don't know, officer.
Are we really going to meet Kum, Jinna?
Yeah.
They're still questioning him right now, and I don't know when they'll finish.
I don't know. It's better than doing nothing.
You haven't changed your mind, have you?
You still don't think Kum did it?
Yeah, I still think so.
- Hello. - Hello.
What are you guys doing here?
We've come to see Kum.
Has he left yet?
He's still being interrogated.
Why are you guys looking for Kum?
Itti, we're certain that Kum isn't the culprit.
Let the police handle it.
You shouldn't vouch for anyone.
But Itti, we're actually very close to Kum.
Those two really loved each other.
It's impossible.
They were in love.
There's no way he would hurt Anda like that.
But he's not cooperating at all.
He's being very suspicious and won't answer any questions.
We haven't been able to let him go yet.
I think he probably has his reasons,
but he definitely wouldn't hurt Anda.
Did Kum and Anda ever have any problems?
Hey.
I'll never break up with you, no matter what.
They never fought at all.
They really loved each other.
Anyway, let the police handle this matter.
You guys can go home now.
I'll be going, then.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
What now?
I don't know.
Art, what on earth are you doing?
You've been fumbling with that for a while.
I was recording.
I saw it in a movie.
They said that no matter what happens, you should always record it.
Record for what?
Well, it's for evidence.
Just in case we miss something, we can listen to it again.
Does anyone have earphones? Let me borrow them.
I think I do. Just a sec.
Thanks.
Here, one each.
Turn up the volume.
I can't hear a thing, Art.
Yeah. Are your earbuds broken, Podduang?
What?
How could that be possible?
Dunk just bought me these.
Could it be a knock-off?
In the livestreams I watch, they always sell items that failed QC.
Better be careful.
You complain so much.
You're using someone else's thing, and you're complaining?
Here, Podduang. Take it.
I have an idea.
I'll put it on the computer in my room so I can listen to it like a detective.
You're way too into this series.
- Let's go. - Hey.
Let's go. See you. We're heading out.
- See you. - See you later.
Let's get going.
I'll give you a ride.
Just keep watching the series.
We're about to reach the climax.
- Are we now? - The climax in...
We're about to reach the climax, right?
- Kum... - The tension's rising.
Kum.
I want us to go public.
I'll leave this to you.
I can handle it just fine myself.
See?
You're always like this.
How can I not love this old dog?
Anda...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Lieutenant, what do you think about that Kum guy?
No matter how you look at it, it's strange.
If we just had a bit more time, we could have gotten something from him.
If it wasn't for the law, I wouldn't have let him go.
By the way, aren't you close to him?
I heard he's been dating your brother for a long time.
Not at all.
Anda never brought him to meet me.
They moved out to live together.
But if Kum is involved in Anda's death,
I won't let him get away with it. You know that, right?
I'm so hungry.
There's nothing to eat in my room.
Do you want anything?
No, you go ahead.
You're really not eating?
Yeah.
Then... I'm getting some.
What are you looking at?
[Jinna: Can I have your beer?]
I sent you a message.
You didn't reply.
I know.
Just a moment.
Why are you giving me this?
What?
Look.
You said you wanted a beer. [Jinna: Can I have your beer?]
Yeah, a beer it is.
But I can't ride home if I drink this.
I know.
I'll drink with you.
Get on the bike. What are you standing there for?
Can you hold this?
How would I ride the bike? I need both hands on the handlebars.
Come here, let me put it on for you.
Have to wear a helmet to stay safe on the road.
Get on.
Here, you go first, or you won't be able to get on.
Is Satang coming back late again?
Yeah.
He's staying at a friend's house tonight.
I guess they'll be gaming all night again.
He never stays home, does he?
If you see him, give him a piece of your mind for me.
He really looks up to you.
So, did drinking beer help with the stress?
Why drink only when I'm stressed?
Why would you think that?
Well, you texted me asking for a beer, so I thought you were stressed.
It was an autocorrection.
Look.
[Can I have your number?]
[Can I have your beer?]
I was wondering why you suddenly asked for a beer.
I was going to ask for your number.
Number?
Like, my number?
Yeah.
What for?
Well, I want it.
How many reasons are there for someone to ask for a number?
Plenty.
You could be trying to sell me insurance.
Or you might be a scammer.
I bet that's it.
That's your side job?
You're weird.
What if it's because I want to make a move?
Make a move?
On me?
I asked for your number to hit on your brother, I guess.
Smartass.
I won't give it to you, then.
Does "it" mean your number or permission to hit on you?
Both.
Can I kiss you, Podduang?
I...
I'd better leave.
I forgot my phone.
Are they really broken?
Dunk, you asshole.
I won't let you borrow my things ever again.
Help me.
Help...
Are you sure it wasn't music?
Yeah.
It's just like I told you.
It came from the earbuds.
Help me, Jinna...
Hey, Jinna.
Do you believe me?
I'm not crazy.
The sound really came from the earbuds.
It was so clear.
It's like...
Someone was speaking right in my ear.
Then would you believe me...
If I told you that I've heard those voices for as long as I can remember?
Jinna.
Your time is up.
Don't cross the road.
Jinna.
Your time is up.
Jinna. Help me...
Jinna. Jinna. Your time is up.
Jinna. Jinna.
Jinna, help me.
Those voices won't stop ringing in my head.
There's nothing I can do about them.
That's why I know that you're not just imagining it.
I've been hearing those voices, too.
Those voices?
The voice you heard from the earbuds is Anda's.
It's the same voice I've been hearing for a while now.
That's not funny, Jinna.
This isn't something to joke about.
Where do you think it came from, then?
I'm not joking, Podduang.
Just believe me.
Anda is still lingering around us.
He really needs our help.
Anda,
if there's anything I can do to help, let me know.
Who did this to you?
Let me help you, Anda.
Your brother just died, Itti.
Won't you even give me time to process this?
Mom, I understand, but look at what this is doing to you.
You can't eat or sleep at all.
You're going to keep drowning in grief forever.
I'm worried about you and Dad.
Anda is already gone.
But as for us, we still have to live on.
Then give me one month before we cremate him.
Mom...
Please let him go.
Itti...
Why won't you listen to me at all?
I asked for three months, and you said no.
Now I'm asking for just one month, and you still say no.
You're really a terrible brother...
You couldn't even protect your brother.
I'm asking for more time with him, and you won't let me have it.
Fine, then it's up to you.
Hey, want to go to that same place after this?
We need to talk about Anda again.
Hello, Satang? I'm at the funeral.
Sure.
Say that again. What happened to the kitchen sink?
The water won't stop running.
I even turned the red valve like you told me to.
What?
Are you sure you turned it the right way?
How could it still be running?
I turned it the right way!
I turned it so hard that I almost broke it.
Wait, hold on.
Just a second.
Hey. Can you hear me?
Hello, Satang?
Can you hear me?
What the hell?
Hello?
Hello? Hey, hello?
Satang, hello?
Podduang...
Help me.
Was it you?
You killed him, didn't you?
You planned the whole thing, didn't you?
Say something!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Just answer me!
Don't be a coward!
I didn't do it.
You didn't? Then what the hell was that chat?
What did you tell the police?
Spit it out!
I told you already. I've told them everything.
You've told them everything?
- Enough already. - Enough.
- Go. - Shit...
This is my brother's funeral.
If you're going to fight like rabid dogs, take it outside.
- Aren't you a cop? - Go.
You should put him in jail!
- He's the one who killed Anda. - Hey.
Just confess already.
- Tell everyone you killed him! - Stop it.
That's enough.
This is going too far.
My parents are sitting right there.
At the very least, show them some respect.
Do you really think that Anda killed himself?
What I think is none of your business.
All you care about is losing your job because my brother died.
Go throw your tantrum somewhere else.
Don't do it at my brother's funeral.
Do you get it now? If you do, please leave.
You ruined my life.
- You bastard! - Go.
Leave.
Podduang!
I don't care whether or not you like Jinna.
He doesn't belong to anyone yet, so let's compete to win him over.
Deal?
Do you want anything? I'll get it for you.
I can buy it myself.
But I'm sure there's something you really want
that money can't buy.
The jacket the vendor is wearing, I bought for Anda.
How did my friend's jacket end up with you?
- I took it from... - From the dead man's car, right?